{"status":"Success","data":{"quiz_datas":[{"question_no":"22","question":"\u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d36\u0d46\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d35\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d ?","option1":"\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d38\u0d3f","option2":"\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d2c\u0d3f","option3":"\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0e","option4":"\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d21\u0d3f","answer":"3"},{"question_no":"45","question":"\u0d38\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d17\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4b \u0d15\u0d1f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d41 \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","option1":"\u0d05\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d","option2":"\u0d2a\u0d38\u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02","option3":"\u0d05\u0d31\u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d1f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d","option4":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d2e\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"302","question":"\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d34\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d31\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d35\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d41 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d23\u0d3f \u0d17\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u200c \u0d35\u0d47\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d ? ","option1":"\u0d32\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d47\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7c","option2":"\u0d0e\u0d38\u0d4d .\u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d15\u0d3f","option3":"\u0d2a\u0d3f .\u0d32\u0d40\u0d32","option4":"\u0d2a\u0d3f.\u0d38\u0d41\u0d36\u0d40\u0d32","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"389","question":"\u0d2a\u0d47\u0d36\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d35\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d28\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d24\u0d32\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4b\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d02","option1":"\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d02 ","option2":"\u0d2e\u0d46\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d38\u0d4d ","option3":"\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d","option4":"\u0d38\u0d46\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2c\u0d46\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d02","answer":"4"},{"question_no":"343","question":"\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d41\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d","option1":"\u0d13\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d1c\u0d7b","option2":"\u0d28\u0d48\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d47\u0d1c\u0d7b","option3":"\u0d39\u0d48\u0d21\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1c\u0d7b","option4":"\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d2c\u0d7a","answer":"3"},{"question_no":"329","question":"\u0d26\u0d42\u0d30\u0d26\u0d7c\u0d36\u0d7b \u0d06\u0d30\u0d02\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d","option1":"1986 \u0d2e\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d 1","option2":"1976 \u0d0f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d7d 1","option3":"1976 \u0d2e\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d 1","option4":"1986 \u0d0f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d7d 1","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"408","question":"\u0d38\u0d57\u0d30\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d25\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d31\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d39\u0d02 :","option1":"\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4b","option2":"\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d38\u0d4d","option3":"\u0d36\u0d28\u0d3f","option4":"\u0d2c\u0d41\u0d27\u0d7b","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"675","question":"\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d34\u0d46\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d31\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d35\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d 2013 \u0d32\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d7c\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d1c\u0d41\u0d28 \u0d05\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d","option1":"\u0d38\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d7b \u0d24\u0d46\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d7d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7c","option2":"\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d39\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3f","option3":"\u0d0e\u0d02.\u0d0e\u0d38\u0d4d.\u0d27\u0d4b\u0d23\u0d3f","option4":"\u0d38\u0d57\u0d30\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d17\u0d3e\u0d02\u0d17\u0d41\u0d32\u0d3f","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"120","question":"\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d31\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d36\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d1f\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d47\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","option1":"\u0d35\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d ","option2":"\u0d24\u0d43\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d36\u0d42\u0d7c","option3":"\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d35\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d02 ","option4":"\u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d42\u0d7c ","answer":"4"},{"question_no":"170","question":"1\/2-1\/30 ?","option1":"1\/10","option2":"1\/18","option3":"1\/20","option4":"1\/15","answer":"2"}]},"code":"100"}
